Tracy Sarah Afram-Owusu

Front-End Developer

Github | aframowusutracysarah@gmail.com | LinkedIn | +233241595499

Professional summary

I am a Front-End Developer with 2 years of experience in web application development. I can analyze customer requirements to create effective, high-end, and user-friendly web solutions. I am a quick learner, capable of adapting to constantly changing requirements and environments. I can work effectively alone or as part of a team.

Project Achievement

- Currently developing a mentorship software for females(Mentees) to get connected to other Software or Web-Inclined Female Mentors.
- Successfully developed an Alumni Management System.
- Successfully developed a portfolio site.
- Successfully developed a mini Blog site.
- Successfully developed a mini To-do app.

Experience

AmaliTech Services, Ghana - *Front-End Developer* OCTOBER 2021- PRESENT

AmaliTech Services, Ghana - *Internship* AUGUST 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2019

TP Connect, Ghana - *Internship* JUNE 2019 - AUGUST 2019

Education

Takoradi Technical University, Bachelor of Technology in Software Engineering JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT

Takoradi Technical University, Higher National Diploma in Information Technology

OCTOBER 2018 - AUGUST 2021

Skills

React

Bootstrap

JavaScript

MySQL

Projects completed

Alumni System

Blog Site

Portfolio Site

To-do App

Tools & Technologies

Git

NPM

PHP Storm

Visual Studio Code

Certifications

Codecademy	Ongoing
Codecademy	Nov. 2021
Codecademy	Nov 2021
Coursera	Dec. 2020
Codecademy	Sep. 2021
	Codecademy Codecademy Coursera

LANGUAGES

English Fante (Native)

Referees

Sharaf Deen Okyere | Account Manager | <u>sharafokyere@gmail.com</u> | +233 24 137 3704 **Kojo Enin Oppan** | Director of ICT | <u>kojo.oppan@ttu.edu.gh</u> | +233 24 609 1283